<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on emmajane.net</title>
    <link>https://emmajane.net/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on emmajane.net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 15:29:11 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://emmajane.net/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About: Emma Jane Hogbin</title>
      <link>https://emmajane.net/about/emma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 15:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emmajane.net/about/emma/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m an expat Canadian living and working on Dartmoor in the UK. During the day I manage the Web operations team for the Digital Services team at the Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs at the United Nations.
Previously, I&amp;rsquo;ve worked for Phase2, and Lullabot. I&amp;rsquo;ve taught Web technologies at both Seneca Collegeand Humber College. I have delivered presentations at conferences across North America, Europe, and New Zealand. My conference presentations have addressed topics that are both &amp;ldquo;technical&amp;rdquo; (database migration, source control, Drupal, front end development) and &amp;ldquo;social&amp;rdquo; (empathy, women in computing, community building).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://emmajane.net/about/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 20:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emmajane.net/about/books/</guid>
      <description>In 2014 I released a set of videos with O&amp;rsquo;Reilly: Collaborating with Git. The companion book, Git for Teams, was released September 2015 and is a best seller. My previous books (Drupal User&amp;rsquo;s Guide; and Front End Drupal) and videos (Drupal Fundamentals) were published with Prentice Hall.
With contributions in Jono Bacon&amp;rsquo;s Linux Desktop Hacks, Earl and Lynette Miles&amp;rsquo; Drupal&amp;rsquo;s Building Blocks, and Shannon Okey&amp;rsquo;s knitting pattern book Alt Fiber, you might say I have a rather diverse (but technical) set of interests.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>